ibroadcast.net 2013-10-23

# iBroadcast - Terms & Conditions

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is, of course, very important to us at iBroadcast. We respect it. 

#### Personally Identifying Information

We collect your name and contact information. We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interactions with our sites and to provide a personalized experience. 

#### Uses

We use personal information to communicate with you, provide you with services, and to help us improve our services. 

#### Cookies

Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. We use cookies on our site to: 

  * help you navigate our website 
  * facilitate the sign up and login process for our services 
  * personalize your experience 
  * analyze which pages our site visitors visit 

#### How We Share Your Personally Identifying Information

Normally we do not, however we may disclose your personally identifying information: 

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process 
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a written government request 
  * if iBroadcast becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personally identifying information becomes subject to a different privacy statement 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so 

We will share your personally identifying information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Statement. We do not otherwise sell your personally identifying information to third parties. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Statement

Please note that this Privacy Statement may change from time to time. If we change this privacy statement in ways that affect how we use your personally identifying information, we will advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes. We will also either post a notice on our home page that this Privacy Statement has changed or send an email to all registered users.
